A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Cultural Interests, Series E FA314
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Organizations and Parks
  - Organizations and Parks - The Pilgrims, 1925-1960 (Box 108, Folder 969)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. became a member, 1925. Nelson A. Rockefeller and Winthrop Aldrich were also members. Invitations to attend dinners usually declined. Society's tribute to Winthrop Aldrich. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
    169P3
  - Organizations and Parks - The Pilgrims, 1925-1960 (Box 108, Folder 0969A)
    David Rockefeller was a member. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
  - Organizations and Parks - Park Association of New York City, 1926-1961 (Box 108, Folder 970)
    Formerly called Central Park Association. Organized to protect Central Park from encroachment and neglect. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. given scroll in honor of his gift and of Tryon Park. Correspondents include Thomas B. Appleget, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    169P4
  - Organizations and Parks - Pan American Society, 1940-1957 (Box 108, Folder 971)
    For promotion of cultural and social relations. G. S. Franklin, Nelson A. Rockefeller's assistant, became member, 1940. Mexican art show arranged by Nelson A. Rockefeller; in 1944, Nelson A. Rockefeller awarded Gold Medal. In 1948, David Rockefeller joined. Nelson A. Rockefeller a member of Board of Directors until 1949; gave $500 annually till 1957. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. attended some dinners. Correspondents John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Evan Young.
    169P5
  - Organizations and Parks - Provident Loan Society of New York, 1908-1946 (Box 108, Folder 972)
    In 1908, John D. Rockefeller subscribed $200,000 for certificates of Society, gave certificates to Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board (GEB). John D. Rockefeller 3rd declined membership, 1946. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Starr J. Murphy.
    169P6
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - United Chapters, 1917-1928 (Box 108, Folder 973)
    Small contributions by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. opposes idea of honorary membership in society. Declined presidency, invitations to speak. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. a member of the Senate, 1922-1928. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    169P7
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - United Chapters - Dedication of New Building, William and Mary College, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 974)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declined to speak, but attended ceremonies. Of special interest because Williamsburg restoration grew out of meeting with William A. R. Goodwin in 1926. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - United Chapters - Membership in Senate - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1922-1928 (Box 109, Folder 975)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. elected to Senate, 1922; resigned due to over-work, 1928; not active, though attended some meetings.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa, 1925-1957 (Box 109, Folder 976)
    Miscellaneous requests and invitations declined. By-laws; handbooks. In 1954, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $250,000 to help rebuild Phi Beta Kappa Memorial Hall at William and Mary College. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Robert W. Gumbel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. A. Shimer.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - Phi Beta Kappa Alumni of New York, 1926-1961 (Box 109, Folder 977)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines presidency and other offices; in 1947, became Life Member. Nelson A. Rockefeller a member.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - Alpha Chapter (College of William and Mary), 1938-1959 (Box 109, Folder 978)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. an "associate member." Small contributions, 1944, 1956. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $10,000, 1959.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - Rhode Island Alpha Chapter, 1930-1960 (Box 109, Folder 979)
    Several small contributions; declination of proposed officerships and invitations.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - Phi Beta Kappa Associates, 1940-1959 (Box 109, Folder 980)
    Group organized to raise money for society and promote its program. In 1941, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. became life member; took no active role. Lists of members.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa - David Rockefeller, 1956-1961 (Box 109, Folder 981)
    David Rockefeller elected honorary member of Harvard chapter, 1956; dues payments. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa Endowment Fund Campaign, 1924-1927 (Box 109, Folder 982)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. served on campaign committee and contributed $100,000. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    169P71
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa Endowment Fund Campaign - Endowment Fund Pledge, 1923-1924 (Box 109, Folder 983)
    $1,000 gift toward fund.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa Endowment Fund Campaign - 1925 Pledge, 1925-1926 (Box 109, Folder 984)
    Gift of $25,000 toward expenses, $75,000 to fund.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa Endowment Fund Campaign - Providence Address, 1926 (Box 109, Folder 985)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. speech stressing importance of education; no copy here.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa Foundation, 1923-1936 (Box 109, Folder 986)
    Organization and background; plans for memorial building and William and Mary College. Fund campaign; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gift and personal interest. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phi Beta Kappa Foundation - Gift for Headquarters, 1927-1933 (Box 110, Folder 987)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. purchased apartment in New York City as Foundation office.
  - Organizations and Parks - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1948-1960 (Box 110, Folder 988)
    Support for Negro education. John D. Rockefeller 3rd contribution to fund for work in Liberia, speech at dinner in honor of Ralph Bunche. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gift toward "retreat" house in Virginia. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard.
    169P8
  - Organizations and Parks - Phelps-Stokes Fund - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Address, April 20, 1954 (Box 110, Folder 989)
    Notes and text of John D. Rockefeller 3rd address at tribute to Dr. Channing Tobias.
  - Organizations and Parks - Park Avenue Association, 1938-1961 (Box 110, Folder 990)
    Regular contributions to Memorial Christmas Tree fund by Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Martha Baird Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    169P9
  - Organizations and Parks - Park Avenue Association, 1938-1961 (Box 110, Folder 0990A)
    Regular contributions to Memorial Christmas Tree fund by David Rockefeller.
  - Organizations and Parks - Royal Society of London, 1939-1960 (Box 110, Folder 991)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. elected a fellow of England's leading scientific organization. Small contributions for special purposes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    169R
  - Organizations and Parks - Tolstoy Foundation, Inc., 1939-1961 (Box 110, Folder 992)
    Daughter of Leo Tolstoy heads organization to aid Russian exiles. Description of activities. Appeals declined until 1956. Correspondents include Alexandra Tolstoy.
    169R1
  - Organizations and Parks - Tolstoy Foundation, Inc., 1939-1961 (Box 110, Folder 0992A)
    Appeals declined until 1956 David Rockefeller nonrecurring $2,500 gift.
  - Organizations and Parks - Safety Societies, 1922-1958 (Box 110, Folder 993)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. a member of committee sponsoring a public safety campaign in New York City; other requests for participation in safety movements declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
    169S
  - Organizations and Parks - Safety Societies - American Museum of Safety, 1910-1935 (Box 110, Folder 994)
    Two small contributions by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Organizations and Parks - National Safety Council, 1917-1958 (Box 110, Folder 995)
    Council activities, safety drives. From 1926-1931, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions total $157,000. 1947, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. endorsement. Laurance S. Rockefeller declines appeals. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Edgar B. Young, Dana S. Creel.
    169S1
  - Organizations and Parks - National Safety Council - Pledges, 1926-1932 (Box 110, Folder 996)
    In 1926, a 5-year conditional pledge for up to $177,000 for public safety work. 1929-1931, conditions on gift removed.
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1951-1955 (Box 111, Folder 997)
    Corporation organized to take over Philipse Castle and Sunnyside from the Tarrytown Historical Society. Dr. Rowell's salary and resignation. Cater's five-year development program; discussion of board membership; discussion of policy by Dana S. Creel and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Dana S. Creel, Hugh Grant Rowell, H. D. Cater.
    169S2
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1956-1960 (Box 111, Folder 998)
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Gifts, 1954-1960 (Box 111, Folder 999)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gifts to restoration
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Gift of Gross Property, 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 1000)
    Purchased for use as office of restoration.
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Pension, 1954 (Box 111, Folder 1001)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gift to initiate pension plan for full-time employees.
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Dr. Rowell's Retirement, 1955-1956 (Box 111, Folder 1002)
    Dr. Hugh Grant Rowell's and Mrs. Alice M. Runyon's changing position in Sleepy Hollow Restorations; their retirement.
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Publicity, 1955-1959 (Box 111, Folder 1003)
    Newspaper stories on restoration.
  - Organizations and Parks - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - The Old Dutch Church of Sleepy Hollow, September 1, 1956 (Box 111, Folder 1004)
    Study submitted by Harold Dean Cater, Executive Director of Sleepy Hollow Restorations.
  - Organizations and Parks - Avenue of the Americas Association, 1930-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1005)
    Formerly 6th Avenue Association. Group seeking to get "el" razed and area regenerated. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. a guest of honor at dinner celebrating opening of subway. Renaming of 6th Avenue. Projects for the future. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $6,000 for various projects. Miscellaneous correpondence. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Colonel Jenkins.
    169S3
  - Organizations and Parks - Sons of the Revolution and Sons of the American Revolution, 1895-1961 (Box 112, Folder 1006)
    Two separate but similar patriotic organizations frequently confused with each other. John D. Rockefeller became member of New York chapter of Sons of the American Revolution, after search for proof of the required revolutionary ancestor, 1896. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Nelson A. Rockefeller declined to join. In 1934, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. became member of Virginia Chapter of Sons of the Revolution and donated money for several revolutionary war flags. John D. Rockefeller 3rd and David Rockefeller declined to join Sons of the Revolution. Declinations of appeals; right-wing literature from Major Hagood. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, Dana S. Creel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., George Rogers, Major Hagood.
    169S4
  - Organizations and Parks - Sportsmanship Brotherhood, 1926-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1007)
    Worked with high school boys through local group; stressed fair play. Nominal John D. Rockefeller, Jr. interest. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Mathew Woll, Arthur W. Packard, Daniel Chase.
    169S5
  - Organizations and Parks - Sportsmanship Brotherhood - Contributions, 1926-1932 (Box 112, Folder 1008)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $8,500.
  - Organizations and Parks - Society of the Cincinnati, 1929-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1009)
    Patriotic society founded in 1783, with George Washington as first president. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. an honorary member, 1929; in 1941, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $500; in 1948, he gave $500. In 1959, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. inherited $2.05 from Society member, declined it. All invitations and most appeals declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Robert W. Gumbel.
    169S6
  - Organizations and Parks - Society of Arts and Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 112, Folder 1010)
    An organization with funds looking for a program; awarded medals, aided starving artists, proposed International House project, which was dropped. No Rockefeller involvement. Correspondents include Carl Byoir, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    169S7
  - Organizations and Parks - Sloan Foundation, 1947-1959 (Box 113, Folder 1011)
    Information on Foundation's activities; dinner invitations. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller.
    169S8
  - Organizations and Parks - Sloan Foundation - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1949-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1012)
    In 1950, Laurance S. Rockefeller joined Board of Trustees. Major objectives of Foundation; policy questions. Reports, projects, grants, additions to Board. Copies of several articles on the Foundation; report on Foundation investments. 1952 testimony for Cox investigation. Laurance S. Rockefeller dinner and speech on RBI, 1954. Amended agreement between Memorial Center and Foundation, 1958. Correspondents include Arnold Zurcher, Alfred Sloan, Jr., Karl Compton, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    169S8L
  - Organizations and Parks - Sloan Foundation - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1953-1955 (Box 113, Folder 1013)
  - Organizations and Parks - Sloan Foundation - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1956-1959 (Box 113, Folder 1014)
  - Organizations and Parks - Sloan Foundation - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1960-1961 (Box 113, Folder 1015)
  - Organizations and Parks - Sloan Foundation - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Financial Statements, 1959-1961 (Box 114, Folder 1016)
    Year-end financial statements and auditors reports.
  - Organizations and Parks - Smoke Control, 1933-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1017)
    Information on smoke control organizations; no Rockefeller interest. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    169S9
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Horticultural Society, 1913-1946 (Box 114, Folder 1018)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller were honorary members; made small donations toward prizes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
    169T
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Horticultural Society - Contributions, 1916-1941 (Box 114, Folder 1019)
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, 1938-1940 (Box 114, Folder 1020)
    Dr. Rowell's plans for Society. First mention of Elsie Janis house. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. elected honorary member, 1939; building the collection. The Rockefeller Memorial Room. Riparian rights of Philipse Castle property; offers of furniture; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s service as trustee of Society. Shift of property to Sleepy Hollow Restorations. Nominal family memberships after 1953. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Grant Rowell.
    169T1
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, 1941-1961 (Box 114, Folder 1021)
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - Loans and Gifts, 1943-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1022)
    Gifts totaling $732,876, made during the years 1939-1948.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - Contributions - Abby Rockefeller Milton, 1942-1955 (Box 114, Folder 1023)
    $20,000 in 1942.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - Grove Street Property Sale, 1940-1954 (Box 114, Folder 1024)
    Proposed sale of Society property.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - Westchester County Park Commission - Land Exchange, 1940-1946 (Box 114, Folder 1025)
    Land exchange gave restoration triangular piece, including mill pond.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - Annual Memberships, 1941-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1026)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd were dues-paying members.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - Annual Reports, 1946 (Box 115, Folder 1027)
    Certificate and By-Laws.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - John D. Rockefeller Memorial Room, 1938-1950 (Box 115, Folder 1028)
    Hugh Grant Rowell asks for some appropriate Rockefeller items. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s interest; planning the Memorial Room. 1939 opening of room. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. paid for necessary work; additional gifts for room. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Grant Rowell, Arthur W. Packard.
    169T1A
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - John D. Rockefeller Memorial Room - Family Loans and Gifts, 1939-1962 (Box 115, Folder 1029)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gifts of John D. Rockefeller items to Society; arrangements for gifts of various items belonging to John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller to be given to Society; John D. Rockefeller desk, pictures, chairs, books. Consideration of the Museum of the City of New York as alternate depository. Decision to discontinue Memorial Room; distribution of items to John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s children proposed. Correspondents John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Dana S. Creel.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - John D. Rockefeller Memorial Room - Inventory, 1942-1966 (Box 115, Folder 1030)
    Inventory of contents of room.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - John D. Rockefeller Memorial Room - Clippings, 1939-1948 (Box 115, Folder 1031)
    Newspaper accounts of Memorial Room.
  - Organizations and Parks - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns - John D. Rockefeller Memorial Room - Mrs. E. B. Schmidt, 1942-1947 (Box 116, Folder 1032)
    Interior decorator who helped in furnishing of Philipse Castle; purchase and commissions paid for by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Organization and Meetings, 1942-1961 (Box 116, Folder 1033)
    1943 organizational and administrative chart; by-laws; reports on Board meetings. Merger of Philipse Castle and Sunnyside restorations via Sealantic Fund. Dr. Hugh Grant Rowell's final report; 1953 revision of by-laws. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, Dana S. Creel.
    169T1B
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Reorganization, 1941 (Box 116, Folder 1034)
    Dr. Rowell's apprehensions regarding any future attempt to gain control of Philipse Castle as a source of personal profit; his desire for self-perpetuating Board. Proposed reorganization; the Todd Bill; changing of name to Historical Society of the Tarrytowns. New By-Laws. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. Belknap, Dr. Hugh Grant Rowell.
    169T1B1
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Pledges for Furnishings and Research, 1940-1944 (Box 116, Folder 1034A)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. payments on pledges toward Philipse Castle restoration work; negotiations for furnishings. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Grant Rowell.
    169T1C
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Pledges for Furnishings and Research, 1945-1948 (Box 116, Folder 1035)
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Pledges for Furnishings and Research - Pledge, February 8, 1940 (Box 116, Folder 1036)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. pledge toward purchase of Elsie Janis property as new home for historical society.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Letters of Gift, 1944-1948 (Box 117, Folder 1037)
    For furnishings and other development of the Castle.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Philipse Castle Restoration Memo, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 1038)
    Memo regarding total of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gifts to Castle and Sunnyside up to 1949.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - April 1944 Gift - Rowell's Salary, 1944-1948 (Box 117, Folder 1039)
    Hugh Grant Rowell.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Pledges, June 1942, July 1942, et al., 1942-1943 (Box 117, Folder 1040)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s "final" pledge, and other pledges. List of 1940-1942 pledges. Also Hugh Grant Rowell's 1943 proposals for post-war projects.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - January 1946 Underwriting of Budget (Box 117, Folder 1041)
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - 1947 Underwriting of Budget, 1946-1947 (Box 117, Folder 1042)
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Pledges, April 1940, 1941, 1942, 1940-1942 (Box 117, Folder 1043)
    Gifts by Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Dr. Hugh Grant Rowell Account, 1943-1944 (Box 117, Folder 1044)
    Dr. Rowell handled expenses at restoration for John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; reported on them to him and was reimbursed. Corespondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Grant Rowell.
    169T1C1
  - Organizations and Parks - Tarrytown Historical Society - Investments, 1941-1944 (Box 117, Folder 1045)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. has Barton Turnbull and Bertram Cutler study society's investments; suggested changes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Grant Rowell, Bertram Cutler, Barton Turnbull.
    169T1D
  - Organizations and Parks - Elsie Janis Property - Philipse Manor, 1928-1939 (Box 117, Folder 1046)
    Manor first offered to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. for apartment house development; Civic League obtained Abby Aldrich Rockefeller pledge toward purchase of house, 1931. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. interested, but unwilling to help purchase it. Bank took over property through foreclosure, and Tarrytown Historical Society became actively interested. Up till 1939, no acceptable price was agreed upon between John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and bank. Correspondents include Elsie Janis, Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Grant Rowell.
    217
    Closed material in Folder 1046A was opened per KWR 08/23/2006. Material was reintegrated into Folder 1046 by DA 10/08/2008.
  - Organizations and Parks - Elsie Janis Property - Philipse Manor - Letters of Appreciation, 1940 (Box 117, Folder 1047)
    Thanking John D. Rockefeller, Jr. for buying property.
    Closed material in Folder 1047A was opened per KWR 08/23/2006. Material was reintegrated into Folder 1047 by DA 10/08/2008.
  - Organizations and Parks - Philipse Castle, 1939-May 1940 (Box 117, Folder 1048)